

PROFILE OF

| Name/Surname: | | |
|----------------|--|--|
| SIAMAK/GHAFARI | | |



Please insert your digital photo here (max. 50KB) >>>

| Personal Details | |
|-------------------------|--|
| Date and Place of Birth | 10/22/1977 |
| Nationality | Iranian |
| | No 30. Goodarzi dead eand, Hatefi alley, Shahabi st., Kashani sholai |
| Permanent Address | Ave., Boroujerd city, Lorestan |
| Phone | 06642534047 |
| Mobile | 09354052684 |
| E-Mail | siamak.ghafari@yahoo.com |
| Skype | |
| Marital Status | |
| Children | 2 Age: 5 |
| Relocation | ⊠ yes □ no |

Career Expectations (in which position do you see your professional future)

Strategic, academic, economic and marketing researches. Data analysis, statistical analysis using SPSS, Eviews, Lisrel, STATA software, data mining and data gathering. Field researches. Civil engineering and building structural and seismotic behavioral analysis and simulation (MATLAB). English to Persian translation- Marketing and sales- Management- Accounting Market analysis

| Education and Professional Qualification | |
|--|---------------------------------|
| mm.yy – mm.yy | Name of the University , Degree |
| | Microbiology |
| | Finantial management |
| | Acounting |
| | English |
| | Computer |

| Languages (Native) (Fluent) (Working knowledge) | PersianEnglishArabic |
|---|--|
| (Beginner) | |



| Computer Skills | MS.Office - SPSS- MATLAB- Eviewa-Opensees- STATA Photoshop Internet | | | |
|--|---|--|--|--|
| | | | | |
| | T | | | |
| Driving License | yes no Class: 2 | | | |
| | | | | |
| Employment History | | | | |
| mm.yy – mm.yy | Name of the Company, Place, Specialization of the company Jobtitle Responsibilities Acchievements | | | |
| 2007 - | Easy Trading Group/Head of research and marketing and founder | | | |
| 2008-2009 | Karaplast industrial group/sales supervisor | | | |
| 2011-2012 2003-2007 | Alvanddokhan/sale expert | | | |
| 2003-2007 | B.A.T/Market supervisor | | | |
| 2002 2003 | Isfahan Central oficce of culture government/Adminstration supervisor | | | |
| Personal Characteristics | | | | |
| Warm, active, positive, participative, energitic, good learner, team worker, good manager/leader | | | | |
| Recommendations | | | | |
| | npany Position Contact Information | | | |
| | | | | |
| | | | | |
| | | | | |
| | | | | |
| Recruiter's Interview Com | ments: | | | |
| | | | | |